{
  "inputTimeWaitSecs": 90,
  "extraDescription": "For products with magnitudes 1 to 20",
  "openingRemarks": "Enter answer as space or comma separated pair of integers.<p>NB: You can also enter 'U' or 'unexpected' if no pair of integers exist to satisfy the demands of the question.",
  "questions": [
    {
      "question": "Find two integers whose product is 20 and whose sum is 9.",
      "answer": "4 5",
      "numberInputTypes": [
        "prequad"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "Find two integers whose product is 18 and whose sum is -9.",
      "answer": "-3 -6",
      "numberInputTypes": [
        "prequad"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "Find two integers whose product is 20 and whose sum is -9.",
      "answer": "-4 -5",
      "numberInputTypes": [
        "prequad"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "Find two integers whose product is -1 and whose sum is 0.",
      "answer": "1 -1",
      "numberInputTypes": [
        "prequad"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "Find two integers whose product is -16 and whose sum is 6.",
      "answer": "-2 8",
      "numberInputTypes": [
        "prequad"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "Find two integers whose product is 12 and whose sum is -8.",
      "answer": "-2 -6",
      "numberInputTypes": [
        "prequad"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "Find two integers whose product is -14 and whose sum is -5.",
      "answer": "2 -7",
      "numberInputTypes": [
        "prequad"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "Find two integers whose product is 8 and whose sum is -6.",
      "answer": "-2 -4",
      "numberInputTypes": [
        "prequad"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "Find two integers whose product is -11 and whose sum is 10.",
      "answer": "-1 11",
      "numberInputTypes": [
        "prequad"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "Find two integers whose product is 10 and whose sum is -7.",
      "answer": "-2 -5",
      "numberInputTypes": [
        "prequad"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "Find two integers whose product is -12 and whose sum is 4.",
      "answer": "-2 6",
      "numberInputTypes": [
        "prequad"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "Find two integers whose product is -13 and whose sum is 12.",
      "answer": "-1 13",
      "numberInputTypes": [
        "prequad"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "Find two integers whose product is -18 and whose sum is -3.",
      "answer": "3 -6",
      "numberInputTypes": [
        "prequad"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "Find two integers whose product is -20 and whose sum is -1.",
      "answer": "4 -5",
      "numberInputTypes": [
        "prequad"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "Find two integers whose product is 11 and whose sum is 12.",
      "answer": "1 11",
      "numberInputTypes": [
        "prequad"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "Find two integers whose product is -5 and whose sum is 4.",
      "answer": "-1 5",
      "numberInputTypes": [
        "prequad"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "Find two integers whose product is -14 and whose sum is 5.",
      "answer": "-2 7",
      "numberInputTypes": [
        "prequad"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "Find two integers whose product is -3 and whose sum is 2.",
      "answer": "-1 3",
      "numberInputTypes": [
        "prequad"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "Find two integers whose product is -13 and whose sum is -12.",
      "answer": "1 -13",
      "numberInputTypes": [
        "prequad"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "Find two integers whose product is -17 and whose sum is 16.",
      "answer": "-1 17",
      "numberInputTypes": [
        "prequad"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "Find two integers whose product is -7 and whose sum is 6.",
      "answer": "-1 7",
      "numberInputTypes": [
        "prequad"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "Find two integers whose product is 16 and whose sum is -8.",
      "answer": "-4 -4",
      "numberInputTypes": [
        "prequad"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "Find two integers whose product is 16 and whose sum is -10.",
      "answer": "-2 -8",
      "numberInputTypes": [
        "prequad"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "Find two integers whose product is -19 and whose sum is -18.",
      "answer": "1 -19",
      "numberInputTypes": [
        "prequad"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "Find two integers whose product is -10 and whose sum is -3.",
      "answer": "2 -5",
      "numberInputTypes": [
        "prequad"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "Find two integers whose product is -7 and whose sum is -6.",
      "answer": "1 -7",
      "numberInputTypes": [
        "prequad"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "Find two integers whose product is -8 and whose sum is 2.",
      "answer": "-2 4",
      "numberInputTypes": [
        "prequad"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "Find two integers whose product is 16 and whose sum is 10.",
      "answer": "2 8",
      "numberInputTypes": [
        "prequad"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "Find two integers whose product is 19 and whose sum is -20.",
      "answer": "-1 -19",
      "numberInputTypes": [
        "prequad"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "Find two integers whose product is 2 and whose sum is -3.",
      "answer": "-1 -2",
      "numberInputTypes": [
        "prequad"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "Find two integers whose product is 4 and whose sum is 4.",
      "answer": "2 2",
      "numberInputTypes": [
        "prequad"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "Find two integers whose product is 20 and whose sum is -12.",
      "answer": "-2 -10",
      "numberInputTypes": [
        "prequad"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "Find two integers whose product is -20 and whose sum is 1.",
      "answer": "-4 5",
      "numberInputTypes": [
        "prequad"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "Find two integers whose product is -6 and whose sum is 1.",
      "answer": "-2 3",
      "numberInputTypes": [
        "prequad"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "Find two integers whose product is -2 and whose sum is -1.",
      "answer": "1 -2",
      "numberInputTypes": [
        "prequad"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "Find two integers whose product is 1 and whose sum is 2.",
      "answer": "1 1",
      "numberInputTypes": [
        "prequad"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "Find two integers whose product is 1 and whose sum is -2.",
      "answer": "-1 -1",
      "numberInputTypes": [
        "prequad"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "Find two integers whose product is -11 and whose sum is -10.",
      "answer": "1 -11",
      "numberInputTypes": [
        "prequad"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "Find two integers whose product is 3 and whose sum is 4.",
      "answer": "1 3",
      "numberInputTypes": [
        "prequad"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "Find two integers whose product is 19 and whose sum is 20.",
      "answer": "1 19",
      "numberInputTypes": [
        "prequad"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "Find two integers whose product is -8 and whose sum is -2.",
      "answer": "2 -4",
      "numberInputTypes": [
        "prequad"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "Find two integers whose product is 20 and whose sum is 12.",
      "answer": "2 10",
      "numberInputTypes": [
        "prequad"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "Find two integers whose product is 2 and whose sum is 3.",
      "answer": "1 2",
      "numberInputTypes": [
        "prequad"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "Find two integers whose product is -18 and whose sum is 7.",
      "answer": "-2 9",
      "numberInputTypes": [
        "prequad"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "Find two integers whose product is 4 and whose sum is -4.",
      "answer": "-2 -2",
      "numberInputTypes": [
        "prequad"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "Find two integers whose product is -12 and whose sum is -1.",
      "answer": "3 -4",
      "numberInputTypes": [
        "prequad"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "Find two integers whose product is -2 and whose sum is 1.",
      "answer": "-1 2",
      "numberInputTypes": [
        "prequad"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "Find two integers whose product is 9 and whose sum is -6.",
      "answer": "-3 -3",
      "numberInputTypes": [
        "prequad"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "Find two integers whose product is -4 and whose sum is 0.",
      "answer": "2 -2",
      "numberInputTypes": [
        "prequad"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "Find two integers whose product is 3 and whose sum is -4.",
      "answer": "-1 -3",
      "numberInputTypes": [
        "prequad"
      ]
    }
  ]
}